To rescue their father, they must save the universe.
A Wrinkle in Time is a drama, science fiction, family
film directed by John Kent Harrison.
Meg and Charles Wallace are aided by Calvin and three interesting women in the
search for their father who disappeared during a government experiment.
Their travels take them around the universe to a place unlike any other.
Meg Murry, played by Katie Stuart.
Calvin O'Keefe, played by Gregory Smith.
Charles Wallace Murry, played by David Dorfman.
Dr. Jack Murry, played by Chris Potter.
The Man With Red Eyes, played by Kyle Secor.
Happy Medium, played by Sean Cullen.
A Wrinkle in Time is a 2003 television fantasy film directed by John
Kent Harrison from a teleplay by Susan Shilliday.
The film, a Canadian and U.S.
production, is based on the 1962 novel of the same name by Madeleine L'Engle.
It is produced by Walt Disney Television, Miramax/Dimension Television,
Fireworks Entertainment, and The Kerner Entertainment Company.
The film stars Katie Stuart, Gregory Smith, David Dorfman, Chris Potter, Kyle Secor, Seán
Cullen, Sarah-Jane Redmond, Kate Nelligan, Alison Elliot, and Alfre Woodard.
A Wrinkle in Time premiered at the Toronto Children's film Festival on
April 24, 2003, where it won the Best Feature Film Award.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.